Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
I hope you're having a great day.
希望你今天过得愉快。
I'm happy that you have come this far!
我很高兴你已经走到这一步！
You should be proud of yourself.
你应该为自己感到自豪。
My name is Mark, and I'll be your professor today.
我叫马克，今天我将是你的教授。
This is lesson number two.
这是第二课。
Today, we're talking about an important sugar trap.
今天，我们要谈论一个重要的糖陷阱。
Sugar can sneak into our daily lives without us noticing.
糖可以在不知不觉中潜入我们的日常生活。
Knowing these traps can help you avoid them.
了解这些陷阱可以帮助你避免它们。
Let's discover trap number 1.
让我们来发现陷阱一。
Trap of the day.
今天的陷阱。
It's called "Just one bite".
它叫做“只吃一口”。
Do you know, when you tell yourself.
你知道吗，当你告诉自己。
"Oh, I'll just take a little bit".
“哦，我就吃一点点”。
Or also.
或者说。
"It's so small it won't do anything".
“它这么小，不会有影响”。
"Look how small it is".
“看看它有多小”。
"It won't have any impact I'm sure".
“我肯定它不会有任何影响”。
Wrong.
错误。
Very wrong haha...
非常错误，哈哈……
Sugar is just calling you.
糖分正在召唤你。
It wants you to take a little bit, so that you take more afterwards.
它想让你尝一点，然后再吃更多。
It's a real trap.
这真的是一个陷阱。
It's exactly like a drug.
它就像毒品一样。
In fact, it is a drug.
事实上，它就是一种毒品。
Producers of sugary foods are drug dealers.
含糖食品的生产者就是毒贩。
It's impossible to stop once you start.
一旦开始就停不下来。
It's best to not take the first bite.
最好不要吃第一口。
So that you don't take bite number 2, bite number 3, and then finish
这样你就不会吃第二口、第三口，然后吃完
the whole thing.
整个东西。
Try to have something that can replace sugar.
尝试找一些可以替代糖的东西。
Something that you like!
是你喜欢的东西！
Like a Banana for instance.
比如香蕉。
Always try to have food that you like around you, but that is also
尽量在身边放一些你喜欢的食物，同时也要
healthy.
健康。
So that you can always replace that sugar bite, with something
这样你就可以随时用更好的东西替代糖分。
better.
更好。
I'll give you a little homework to do for next time.
我给你布置一点作业，下次完成。
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Go to your kitchen.
去你的厨房。
Pick up the most sugary thing that you have, in that kitchen.
拿起你厨房里含糖最多的东西。
Look at it.
看着它。
And then throw it away.
然后把它扔掉。
Yes you heard me.
是的，你没听错。
Throw it away, in the trash.
把它扔进垃圾桶。
Don't worry, this is not food waste.
别担心，这不是食物浪费。
Remember, sugar is a drug.
记住，糖是一种毒品。
It's poison.
它是毒药。
It's bad.
这不好。
Bad for everyone.
对每个人都不好。
Throw it away.
把它扔掉。
Don't pick it back.
不要再捡回来。
You'll see that it will feel very good.
你会发现这感觉很好。
It will feel like change.
这会感觉像是改变。
Like you now have a super power.
就像你现在有了超能力。
Never be afraid to throw away a sugary treat, that you have
永远不要害怕扔掉你在恐慌中买的甜食。
bought out of panic.
你不再恐慌了。
You are not in panic anymore.
你现在可以扔掉它了。
You can now throw it away.
没关系。
It's ok.
你的身体会感谢你。
Your body will thank you.
未来的你会感谢你。
The YOU, from the future, will thank you.
每天记住这些提示。
Remember these tips every day.
了解这些糖陷阱可以帮助你做出更好的选择。
Understanding these sugar traps helps you make better choices.
现在你真正掌控了糖分。
Now you're really in control of sugar.
糖分不再控制你。
Sugar is not in control of you.
感觉良好。
Feel good.
享受一整天的活力吧！
Enjoy having energy all day!
我为我们今天的成就感到高兴。
I'm happy of what we have accomplished today.
我们下节课见。
I'll see you for the next lesson.
祝你有美好的一天。
Have a great day.
Have a great day.